(soothing music)
In modern JavaScript, there are two major paradigms,
object-oriented programming and functional programming.
And so in this section you're gonna learn
everything you need to know
about object-oriented programming in JavaScript.
And this is absolutely essential if you want to become
a professional JavaScript developer.
So, we're gonna dive really deep
into what object-oriented programming actually is
and different ways of implementing it in JavaScript.
And we're gonna start with constructor functions,
then move to ES6 classes
and also talk about object.create.
And by the end of the section,
we will even implement inheritance between classes
using all these different techniques.
So, this is gonna be a full packed section
and so let's dive right in.
(upbeat music)